

NGUYEN THANH TUNG

Fresher Java Web



Apply the acquired knowledge to the development of quality software. At the same time, accumulate experience and knowledge to meet the needs of higher positions. Ready to learn new programming language to serve the needs of work and upgrade my skills

Contact information

Oct 25, 1999

thanhtungnguyen913@gmail.com

0398851652

http://bit.ly/3XfJtsd

Cam Le, Da Nang

Skills

Advanced skills

- Java Core
- -00P
- Spring Boot
- RESTful API
- Servlet and JSP, JSTL
- JDBC
- MySQL
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JQuery, AJAX Basic
- Spring Framework Basic
- Spring Data JPA Basic
- JavaScript, ReactJS Basic, NodeJS Front End

Soft skills

- Ability to work independently and in a team
- Quickly adapt to the working environment, get along quickly.
- Withstand high work pressure.
- Organize, plan and manage time.
- Problem-solving skills.
- Self-study and search skills.

Education

• UNIVERSITY OF ECONOMICS - HUE UNIVERSITY

Financial accountant | 09/2017-09/2021

Graduated - GPA 2.34

CODEGYM HUE PROGRAMMING TRAINING CENTER

Developer 02/2022-11/2022

- Join the course "Bootcamp Java WEB", after more than 1000 hours of learning and practicing, I have learned and matured, developed soft skills and technical skills.
- Trained in effective teamwork skills and gained experience through small projects that included management tools such as Kanban and the application of Scrum principles to projects.

Work experience

• TEXTILE GARMENT INVESTMENT JOINT STOCK COMPANY - THIEN AN PHAT

Intern - General Accounting 03/2019-07/2019

- Perform other duties as assigned by the company's chiefaccountant.
- Participate in and coordinate the periodic internalinspection and control.
- Prepare monthly tax declaration dossiers, quarterly financial statements, annual tax finalization dossiers, and annual financial statements as prescribed.
- Provide data to leaders and functional units when required.

• CODEGYM

Student | 10/2022-11/2022

- Project: MEGA FARM CLEAN FOOD STORE
- Deployment time: 1 month

Office information

- Proficient in using Word, Excel, Power Point....

Language

- English level B1 (Listening, speaking, reading and writing is good)

Certificate of completion of courses at Codegym:

http://bit.ly/3RGZOFy

Accounting certificate

https://bit.ly/3EDZcun

Interests

- · Watch movie
- Eating.
- Play game.
- · Play football.
- Travel and explore.

Reference person

• Mr. NGUYEN HUU ANH KHOA

- Director of CodeGym Hue Center
- Phone: 0935 216 417
- Email: Khoa.nguyen@codegym.vn

Applied knowledge

Number of members: 3 members

- Applied knowledge:
 - MySQL Database
 - Spring Boot API - NodeJs - Dashboard
 - React Client
 - iQuery
 - Bootstrap 4
- Position: Member
- Analyze and design application architecture with the team.
- Manage tasks and group discussions via Jira, Slack.
- Application development according to Scrum model standards.
- Teams using Git Source Version Management.
- Report daily work to Coach.
- Build function to create, delete, edit for: Employee.
- Display customer list Build order management function, change order status, create POS for offline sales.
- Revenue statistics and related items
- Cut the interface for DashBoard page.
- · Brief description:

This is a clean food store management system with the following features:

- The dashboard is for administrative users, admin can use all the functions of the system and the employee is the person with limited features, only using some functions (if there is access to the link below). for admin an error page will be displayed)
- Dashboard page provides many subpages with more than 60 functions for users to easily manage products as well as inventory statistics and business status.
- A client page for customers to use. Customers can view and order products on sale. In addition, to help customers choose the desired product, the customer page has the function of filtering by price, brand, and other specifications.
- Link set function description: http://bit.ly/3YrKdf1
- watch video description about project if link crashed: (https://bit.ly/3HWHMdM)
- Link product:

-Client: <u>http://bit.ly/40CWS0H</u> Email: customer@gmail.com

Password: 123123

- Dashboard: https://bit.ly/3REP4Hp

+ Account Admin: Email: bob@co.cc Password: 123 +Account User:

Email: camap@co.cc Password: 12345678

(Note: Customers can view products, add products to the cart and can view and change the cart, but customers who want to pay for products in the cart must log in to their account (or register if you do not have an account) will be paid for the product.)

• Link git:

- Link API: http://bit.ly/3Y8xdLr

- Link Dashboard: http://bit.ly/3lhFA9f

- Link Client: http://bit.ly/3wZUWS2